(Amy:)Why is nothing easy
with him?
(Leonard:)Look, here's the thing you need
to understand about Sheldon:
(Leonard:)he's the worst.
(Amy:)I prefer to think of it
as high-maintenance.
(Leonard:)I prefer to think of myself
as five-ten,
(Leonard:)but I still need to get
all my pants hemmed.
(Amy:)I guess I should have known
what I was getting myself into.
(Leonard:)Don't beat yourself up.
(Leonard:)You've never lived
with anyone before.
(Amy:)That's true.
And you're starting out
(Leonard:)with Sheldon Cooper.
(Leonard:)That's like getting your first
pet and having it be--
(Raj:)I don't know...
(Leonard:)What's a kind of pet
that ruins your life?
(Amy:)You're not making me
feel better.
(Leonard:)Look, even when Penny and I
started living together,
there was a-a learning curve.
(Leonard:)But I promise you,
it does get easier.
(Amy:)He put a sign up in the bathroom
that says,
"Number of days
without Amy's hair on the soap."
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)My record was six.